MkvDrama.net
(This program is intended
for viewers aged 18 and over.)
(It may contain content
depicting inappropriate behavior)
(violence, sexual content,
and strong language.)
(Viewer discretion is advised.)
(This series is entirely fictional
and does not depict)
(any real individuals, locations,
organizations, or events.)
What are you drawing?
Have you guys come up
with a team name yet?
P'Toobtub is hounding me for it.
Check this out. "Born As Alpha."
Man, I'm a total genius.
I'm super cool, super smart,
and super dangerous.
Literally,
I'm born to be
the leader of the pack.
Oh, my God. That's so freaking cool.
I've got one issue with it, though.
What?
I feel like if we lose,
we'll end up looking
more like lost puppies than alphas.
Then don't lose.
You're always killing the vibe.
Think of one yourself, then. Go on.
- Try coming up with a name.
- Yeah.
I've got nothing.
So you can't think of anything?
And all you did was judge me.
If not this one, then what?
It's cool as hell, man.
This is the one. "Born As Alpha."
Guys, I figured it out.
How about "Number"?
Huh? Number?
Yeah, Number.
Your name, Three, is a number.
Ten is a number, too.
Wait...
What about Jack?
Isn't that a face card?
It's not a number.
But it sits right next to a number,
meaning I'm right beside you two.
Wait...
You're Jack, and Jack sits next to Ten.
What about me?
I'm so freaking lonely, man.
Poor you.
Since our first year.
- Fine. We don't have to use it.
- No, let's use it.
It's pretty cool.
- Are you crazy?
- Hey!
If anyone ever asks...
where the team name came from,
we can say with total confidence that
it came from our names.
Wow, that's so cool.
But if we spell it N-U-M-B-E-R,
it's not that cool.
How should we spell it?
Where are you going?
Here.
- Three, what are you doing?
- Hey, hey!
What?
P'Toobtub is gonna give you an earful.
An eraser will take it right off.
If it wouldn't come off,
I wouldn't have written it.
You think I'm crazy?
What if P'Toobtub yells at me?
Look!
Numb2r!
So damn cool.
- Works for me.
- I know.
Just you watch.
One day, we're going to be number one
and lift the trophy on stage.
Who are you looking at?
Hey, hey, hey!
Sh*t.
- P'Toobtub's here! Remove it.
- What the hell are you doing?
Three, what the hell are you doing?
I've been away for one second...
- You're such a pain in the ass.
- You can see it?
It's invisible ink, bro.
- You've got magic eyes.
- Remove it right now!
Man...
Remove it!
- I am... I'm outta here!
- Where do you think you're going?
- What the hell are you waiting for?
- Are you gonna remove it or not?
- The eraser...
- See you, P'Toobtub.
Hey, hey!
- Remove...
- Three!
Don't be cheeky. Remove it.
You got it. Sure.
You go first. Go ahead.
- I'm not staying. See ya!
- What the hell?
Jeez, you made a total mess.
Get over here!
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Every time, it's just me and me only♪
♪What's this feeling? I've got no clue,♪
♪Could it be I'm missing you?♪
♪(Am I missing you?)♪
♪Birthday but with me♪
♪Why is it always happening to me?♪
♪The more it happens, the more I see♪
♪Yeah, it must be♪
Chiang Mai, I'm here!
Whoa, Soh!
Should we start at Doi Suthep?
Let's go pay our respects
for some good luck.
After that, we'll head over to Nimman
to hit all the famous landmarks.
Then in the afternoon,
we'll go to Tha Phae.
In the evening, we'll go see your mom.
And tomorrow, let's go to Mon Cham.
Sound good?
But we're going to be here
for three whole days.
We can take our time.
I'm not going to run off.
I'm just so excited.
I mean, since we're in your hometown,
I want to go everywhere with you.
Chiang Mai, here I come!
Why do you look so cute today?
You're adorable,
and look at your outfit.
You look so cute and cuddly.
Come on, let's sing.
- ♪I brought some carrots for you♪
Hey, hey!
Uh... I'm sorry. Sorry, my bro.
My bad. My bad.
Chiang Mai, baby!
What's up?
P'Three!
Why the long face?
I bumped into them, not you.
You're looking at me
like I just stepped on your toes.
I'm just...
starving.
I didn't eat a thing on the plane.
Oh, you're hungry?
Hey, that works out.
I just talked to Preaw.
Where are we heading first?
- Nimman.
- And after that, we're off to...
Tha Phae.
Whoa, and after that,
we're going to pay our respects at...
Doi Suthep.
And then we'll go see the mist up at...
- Mon Cham, bro.
- It'll be absolutely perfect.
Anyway, wait a sec. Look at this.
Welcome to Chiang Mai, P'Three.
- Welcome!
- Let's go call a ride.
- Come with us.
- We're gonna grab some food.
Want to keep it cool?
It's written all over your face.
All those guys are here, too.
I thought I was finally gonna have
a date with just the two of us.
This is not what I planned.
Just being together
is good enough, isn't it?
Oh, come on.
Let's go, P'Three.
- We're at the market!
- This is Kad Laung.
- Everything looks so good. Look!
- Look at these coconut rolls.
Everything looks delicious, right?
My mouth is watering. Look.
You want some?
I'm already full.
Soh, I got something on my lips.
Can you wipe it off for me?
(Just being together really is enough.)
Soh, just use a tissue.
- P'Laem, come on.
- Whoops!
Oh, come on...
Look, there's so much good food here.
Here, want some? You hungry?
- Are you hungry?
- I want some pork cracklings.
Pork cracklings!
Where?
(Just being together like this...)
(is...)
There's so much tasty stuff over there.
- Let's go.
- Sure.
Hey, wait.
What are you standing around for?
Hurry up.
Come with me.
Trying watermelon smoothie...
- ASMR.
- Exactly.
Ultra smooth.
We're looking pretty good.
We? I think it's just me.
Buying clothes for P'Toobtub's baby.
Beautiful!
- This one's handsome.
- You again?
My legs are killing me, guys.
Wow, this is pretty.
Shall we take a selfie together?
Okay, fine.
- You look gorgeous.
- Alright.
(Just being together like this...)
Taking a selfie?
What? We're all right here.
Why are you two taking a pic by yourselves?
Come on, hurry up!
- Come on.
- One, two, three!
(Just being together...)
(is enough.)
(Just being together like this...)
(isn't enough, damn it!)
Come on down.
Here, P'Three.
I don't think my mom is home yet.
She's probably still at the hospital.
Is your mom sick?
No, she's a doctor.
- Oh.
- I see.
You scared me. So she's a doctor.
- Wait!
- Wait, what?
I forgot something.
Forgot what?
My toothbrush.
Whoa.
You totally startled me.
Can you take me down to buy one?
You can just order it on an app.
I think you can do that.
There are plenty of apps these days.
- On the phone?
- Yeah.
In this day and age...
Jack.
Will they deliver all the way up here?
Of course they will.
Motorbikes can come all the way up here.
- Right here.
- Uh...
Guys, I want to go see Ava.
- Huh?
- What?
Who?
The tiger with the pretty eyes.
We can stop for Preaw's toothbrush
on the way back.
What's wrong with you?
Are you sick or something?
You're acting weird.
Maybe Soh's mom
needs to give you a check-up.
- Let's just go.
- Alright, let's go.
- Am I getting a toothbrush today?
- What?
Same side.
- Making me sit in the back again?
- Just like always.
Get there safe, guys.
Everyone wants to see Ava anyway.
Guys, see you!
Yes! You finally left!
Man, you were being
third wheels for so long.
Why didn't you leave sooner?
Why did you even come?
Finally alone, just the two of us.
This way, P'Three.
This is my room.
Wait.
So, we finally get to be alone.
Just the two of us. Finally.
I want to stay like this forever.
Can we just stay like this for a while?
You don't have to
look so grumpy anymore
- since...
- I'm happy now.
it's just the two of us now.
Perfect.
Derya, my dear!
Oom-GG-NO-EZ is here to see you!
Oh...
Oom, how did you get here?
I picked her up myself.
When she found out you were coming,
she was so excited.
By the way,
where are your other friends?
You told me to prepare
so many guest rooms.
They're probably out
looking for places to visit, Mom.
They'll likely be back by this evening.
Mom, this is P'Three,
the one I told you about.
Hel... Oh...
Hello.
I see.
The one who recruited you
for the Pro League team?
That's right.
P'Three,
this is Oom, my friend.
She's my best friend from school.
Oh, a best friend.
More than just a best friend.
Oom understands Soh better than anyone.
Where there's Oom, there's Soh.
Where there's Soh, there's Oom.
These two were joined at the hip.
I even thought they were dating.
Mom, what are you even saying?
Wow.
I didn't know sai oua
could smell this amazing.
Look at this sticky rice.
It's perfectly steamed.
- Your cooking is incredible, Mom.
- Oom actually made it.
Soh, have some of this.
Give me your plate.
I'll get some for you.
It must be hard
to find food like this in Bangkok.
- Here, eat up.
- Thanks.
This one, too.
- Thanks, Oom.
- Take this one, too.
Soh, try some nam prik ong.
I know you like spicy food. Here.
Soh doesn't like tomatoes.
P'Three, make sure you eat a lot.
Here, Oom. You should eat up as well.
You're too busy serving everyone.
You're so tiny yourself.
Thanks, Mom.
Oh, tomorrow is
your wedding anniversary, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
I'm planning to go donate things
up on the mountain, like every year.
What a shame. I'm busy this year.
If I weren't, I would go help you
like I always do.
It's alright, dear.
I think I'll ask Soh's friends
to help with the heavy lifting.
Would that be okay?
Oh...
Absolutely, Mom.
When it comes to...
anything involving manual labor,
I'm your man.
I've never been outmatched.
Then this auntie
will be counting on you.
Alright.
- Oom, let's eat.
- Go ahead, Mom.
Here.
Eat up. Let me get this for you.
I really put my heart into this dish.
- Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Have as much as you'd like.
Let me serve you.
Serve some for Soh, too.
Oh, he's fine.
I'm so full, Soh.
Like, I'm stuffed.
I didn't think
you'd finish everything like that.
My mom made quite a lot
since she was planning to
give some to others, too.
Oh, don't worry about that.
To win her heart
and become her favorite son-in-law,
I could eat even more than this.
If your mom makes more,
I'll keep eating.
But...
no matter how I try
to win your mom's heart,
she's still going to prefer Oom anyway.
She likes Oom more than me.
If she tries to block me
and pushes you two to date,
where does that leave me, Soh?
But I like you, P'Three.
That's already a win.
You don't even have to compete.
Besides, as for me and Oom,
it's absolutely impossible
because the person
Oom actually likes is...
you.
What?
Me?
You mean me?
Your cooking is incredible, Mom.
Well, when I was seeing her out,
we chatted for a bit,
and I found out that she's been
a fan of yours for quite some time.
I see.
And the reason
she was acting so indifferent...
is actually because she was just shy.
But it's not that surprising.
If I got to meet my favorite gamer,
I probably wouldn't know
how to act, either.
Is your favorite gamer me?
Well...
it has to be you, obviously.
You feel better now, right?
Not quite.
Oh...
If you could just tell me
you like me one more time,
I'd definitely have sweet dreams
until morning.
I wasn't really ready
when you said it just now.
Come on, just one more time. Please...
Oh?
I think I'm getting sleepy now.
- Hey!
- Should we just head to bed?
- Seriously?
- We have to wake up early tomorrow
to get everything ready
for the mountain trip.
What?
Come on, don't cry.
My mom is really kind.
She's bound to like you
just as much as I do.
♪I'll find my way
into your heart one day,♪
♪Getting a little closer every day,♪
Goodnight, P'Three.
Goodnight.
♪Until your heart makes room for me♪
I'll leave the loading to you.
I have to head off first.
I told the village chief and the kids
I'd be there at 10 AM.
Sure thing, Auntie.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
You can count on me.
P'Laem, hurry up, will you?
What? Are you nagging me?
Jeez, it's P'Jack's fault.
- What?
- He made me walk around the zoo twice.
- Put it down.
- Put it down and get the next load.
There's still plenty more.
Go on.
Get up there.
No.
Go ahead.
Do it.
I guess your friend
doesn't like me very much.
There's no way I could not like you.
I went all the way to Bangkok
to watch you compete.
I started playing Jungle because of you.
I donated so much I was left
with barely any pocket money.
And now I know...
what I should've done all along
was be honest with you...
and ask for your autograph.
Oh, of course.
Wow, quite a long speech there.
I've been a fan
since you were in Numb2r.
It's a shame that whole thing happened.
Otherwise, I'm sure
Numb2r would've gone far,
maybe even all the way
to the international leagues.
Maybe not.
We weren't really in sync anyway,
and we didn't always see eye to eye.
Thank you.
Well, I'll take my leave now.
It's too bad I can't go with you all.
Anyway, good luck, P'Three.
I'm sure
you'll take first place in the APL.
B.S. Brothers have gotta go for it!
Definitely gotta go for it.
- I'm off, Soh.
- Okay.
- Come visit us often.
- Will do.
- Bye-bye.
- Bye, P'Three.
Okay.
Hello, Mom?
Oh, okay. I'll bring it over.
Sure.
P'Three,
my mom told me
to bring the first-aid kit.
I'm exhausted.
Is it this one?
This one with the keychain?
Yes.
- Okay, I'll put it in the truck, then.
- Alright.
Okay.
Oh...
Soh?
Soh, what's wrong?
I don't know. I think it's a bug.
Here, let me check.
Oh...
There, I got it for you.
There's more, P'Jack.
- Is it red? Can you check?
- It's really red.
- It's totally red.
- It's so itchy.
I'll handle it for you.
Where is it? What's its name?
- It already got away.
- It got away?
- Hey.
- Yes?
Our shifts got swapped.
You're supposed to go to the airport.
Oh, okay. My apologies.
Kids, get the stuff in the truck.
Did he say Sumatra, the island?
- It's "sumater." It means sorry.
- Oh, I see.
♪Pancake rolls♪
- ♪I want some pancake rolls♪
- ♪Pancake rolls♪
- Hey, hey!
- Huh? What?
Sir, stop the car!
What is it?
What the hell?
What are you looking for?
Soh...
What's wrong, P'Three?
I think I lost your mom's first-aid kit.
What's up?
- Long time no see, man.
- You're finally back.
Welcome back, bro.
What's the word?
- It was lonely as hell without you.
- Come on.
- I'm back, buddy.
- Yeah, I couldn't play right at all.
Since you're back,
I've got a ride ready for you.
A red truck?
Yeah, a red truck.
What about a van?
The van is at the hotel,
so I rented a red truck first.
That is so extra, man.
Let's just rent a van.
Don't you get what "OG" means, buddy?
When in Chiang Mai,
you take the red truck.
By the way,
now that you're back,
are you ready for the APL?
You bet I am.
- That's dope.
- Come on, let's go.
Let's go explore the tea plantation!
- One, two, three, go!
- Nice!
- Come on.
- Let's go!
- Wait, wait!
Wait, sir.
I'm sorry.
I actually took the wrong truck.
A customer's belongings
are still inside.
I have to go return them.
I really can't take you anymore.
I'm not sure I understood his accent.
- What?
Sorry, I can't go anymore.
I've already called the other driver.
Just wait a moment.
Okay, thank you.
Hey, wait.
Is it this one?
Man, it's freaking hot.
Help.
Help what?
Hurry up and give me my stuff back.
Well, why don't you try
asking me nicely?
I went out of my way
to bring this back to you, you know.
Maybe I won't give it back at all.
Ten...
I'm giving it back right now. See?
Hurry up, Ten!
It's very hot.
Ugh, I'm thirsty.
Let's head up the mountain, guys.
We've been in the foothill for too long.
Hello, Mom?
Yes, we're almost there.
Whoa, there's a long line
of kids already?
Oh, the first-aid kit?
P'Three is taking good care of it.
Don't worry.
Okay.
Alright, shall we go now?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Start the engine, sir. Let's go.
Go.
What?
I can't go.
Huh? Why can't you?
The car broke down.
What?
Did I wear an unlucky shirt today,
or did I get off on the wrong foot?
What rotten luck!
Sir, are you pulling my leg?
No, I'm not.
Sir, it's been an hour.
Are you almost done?
I've got a mission to complete, sir.
I have to win over my boyfriend's mom!
- Sir!
- P'Three...
I already called my mom
to tell her about the breakdown.
She understands perfectly.
You don't need to worry at all.
Soh, thank you so much,
but I don't want your mom
to be kept waiting.
Sir, has the mechanic arrived yet?
Not yet. It'll be a while.
Could you call and tell them to hurry?
Oh, sure.
Thank you.
Three,
should I call Ten?
Man,
I doubt he'd even show up.
Didn't you see
how happy they were earlier,
seeing us all messy?
Wait...
Waiting for me, weren't you?
Get in, or I might change my mind.
Are you coming or not?
I already knew.
Knew what?
That you'd show up anyway.
They're here!
- They're here.
- We finally made it.
Here we are.
- We're here?
- What is this place?
And are those kids? Look, kids!
Come here, kids! Your Laem is here.
Let's dance! Six seven...
Six seven!
- Six seven!
- Want to take some photos?
Photos! Come on, let's take some photos.
Here's the kit, ma'am.
But where is the hill tribe keychain?
That's very important to me, son.
It can't even be replaced.
But, I...
I'm so sorry.
I'll find it
and return it to you, ma'am.
It was a wedding anniversary gift
that my husband left for me.
No matter what I replace it with,
it won't be the same.
I'm so sorry.
You trusted me to take care of it.
You must be
really disappointed in me, right?
Hey, it's alright.
Let's go donate the things.
The kids have been waiting long enough.
Come on.
Ma'am...
Why aren't you mad at me at all?
I'll save my anger for next time.
This time, it was just a mistake.
Let's just let it go.
But in the future,
Soh might have days
where he makes mistakes, too.
And when that day comes,
I want you to stay calm
and give Soh a chance,
just like I'm giving you one today.
Yes, ma'am.
Hey, why that long face?
My mom wasn't even scolding you.
It's just not cool, Soh.
Meeting your mom for the first time,
and I already messed things up.
There, there.
If my mom sees you
making that face,
she's going to worry even more.
I'm just feeling down.
Feeling better now?
Well, almost.
It would be better
if I got a kiss on this side, too.
You've hit your limit.
Wait, there's a limit?
Soh...
It's so freaking hot.
Is it hot, P'Laem?
Yeah, but first of all...
- Six seven!
Here, take this.
- Don't forget to share.
- Share with each other.
- This is delicious.
- Here it is.
- Don't forget to share.
- Share...
There's only one pack,
and you want them to share?
- Share with you, too.
- Oh, with me? Okay.
- You guys in the back, come!
- Come on!
- Want a book?
- Here you go.
- No one is taking my stuff.
- Yeah.
I've got plenty. Here, want some?
Here, here.
This is super yummy.
Share it, and don't forget
- to save some for me.
- This one is amazing.
Bon appétit.
- Delicious! What did you say?
- Oh, bon appétit.
- Thank you.
- Don't forget!
Books, anyone?
- And this too.
- Hey!
Is Chiang Mai really this small?
How many mountains could there be
in Chiang Mai anyway?
Hey, hey, hey!
Wait a second.
Look.
Hey, kid, where did you find this?
Where did you get this from?
Can I buy it from you? How much?
How about you guys play a match for us?
Bangkok is so far away.
I really want to see you guys compete
with my own eyes.
Calm down.
You really want to see us
play against those guys?
I'll give this keychain to the winner,
so can you guys play a match for me?
Oh, sure.
But you'd better keep your word.
Hey, wait.
Who told you we were going to play?
So, what does "Blue Viper" mean exactly?
A snake that ran out of venom?
If you're this much of a chicken,
why not just change your name
to "Wimp Viper"?
- Wimp Viper sounds better, right?
- Yeah, it suits them.
Forget it. Fine, we'll play.
But you guys have to change your name
to "Big Mouth Brothers," too.
- Big Mouth?
- No problem.
You big-mouth posers.
Why do we have to play RoV against them?
They'll end up
knowing all our strategies.
And who said
we're going to play a normal match?
The game we're about to play
is called...
Celestial Clash: Dark Tea Leaves.
(Celestial Clash: Dark Tea Leaves)
The rules are: those three rows
of the tea plantation...
will represent Top Lane,
Mid Lane, and Bottom Lane.
Each team will have their own basket.
Whichever team fills their basket first
will be considered
to have destroyed the enemy tower.
Did I expect way too much from you?
But you're about to find out...
exactly how powerful
Blue Viper really is.
Oh, since you're talking so much trash,
it means
you're already prepared to lose.
- Prepared to lose?
- In that case...
Let the game begin!
- Hey, that's f*cking cheating!
- Bring it on!
We'd better not lose this, damn it.
Go, Blue Viper!
Let's go, team! Fill the basket.
Right here.
Keep going.
You can do it, P'Three!
Keep it up!
Go, go!
Let's do this, guys!
B.S. Brothers!
Pluck all this, take the championship!
Are you here for the trophy
or just for fun?
Whoa, I didn't know there were chickens
on this mountain!
Cock-a-doodle-doo!
You are the chickens.
I'm gonna peck your eyes out.
Hey, let's focus on quality,
not just speed.
- Yeah, and forget those Vipers.
- Alright.
Focus on quality. Let's go!
You got it.
- Buy Fenrir's Tooth. Get an attack speed item.
- Get me Fenrir's Tooth.
Get the Blade of Eternity.
You won't die. Keep going.
- Alright, deal.
- Move fast!
Hey, Soh!
Put it in!
We need to invade their jungle.
You in?
Let's go. If you're in, I'm in.
Keep going!
Soh, heal me.
You got this!
Now I'm motivated. Let's go!
- P'Three!
- Why are you picking a leaf?
You're supposed to pick tea leaves.
Yeah, pick the tea leaves.
If you can't do that,
you'd better go home and cry.
Whoa!
You're about to find out.
You'll see. It's called teamwork.
Hey! Can I pick this one like this?
- Quick! Faster!
- Let's go!
Got it.
Soh! This one, here!
This is the prime tea tip!
Hey, you okay?
- I'm fine!
- You sure?
Ow, ow!
That's my hair!
My bad, my bad.
- My bad, bro.
- My hair's a mess now.
He must be feeling left out,
having to stand there like an extra.
Whoa, Preaw, are you okay?
I think I twisted my ankle.
How about you get some rest?
It's okay. You stay here.
I'll go by myself.
Wait, aren't you going to play?
Go take her place.
I'm not on that team.
Oh, really? But I've seen you guys
compete on the same team.
Yeah, Number.
Your name, Three, is a number.
Ten is a number, too.
My name sits right next to a number,
meaning I'm right beside you two.
Go rest. I'll sub in for you.
Aren't you with Blue Viper?
How can you play for us?
Why not?
If the RoV league finds out
I switched teams for a tea-picking game,
am I going to get banned?
Go.
Look, tea tips!
- Here, here!
- Soh...
- Put them in!
- I'm here to help.
Yeah, great.
What kind of joke are you playing at?
If it's a joke, then laugh.
Why the serious face?
I don't have time to argue with you.
I'm serious.
Aren't you afraid your teammates
will say you betrayed them?
Screw them.
They're going to trash-talk me anyway.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You've been abandoning me all this time.
And now what?
Did you just realize...
what it's like to be abandoned?
Yeah.
I'm back to help now.
What more do you want?
Don't you think it's a little too late?
P'Three...
If you actually want to help me,
don't make us lose.
Just try to keep up with me.
What the hell?
What's your problem?
- What's wrong with you?
- Why?
What's your deal?
- Why? What's up with you?
- Come on! Bring it on!
Soh, come here.
Blue Viper has more tea leaves.
Bring it!
Easy!
It's fine, Mr. Three.
You might lose this time, but...
- you're gonna lose in the APL anyway.
- Exactly.
- Hey, let's go sip some tea.
- Let's go!
Wait a second.
We only count the young tea leaves.
The mature ones don't count.
Based on the results,
B.S. Brothers is the winner!
What the hell?
- What now?
- What?
- Here we go! Wimp Viper!
- Wimp Viper! Wimp Viper!
- One more time! Wimp Viper!
- Wimp Viper!
You don't have to change the name
to Wimp Viper, though.
We were just teasing, you know.
- Come on, Wimp Viper!
- Wimp Viper!
- It smells so good.
- Truly refreshing.
Hey, kid...
Wait!
Hey...
Where is it?
Where's the thing you promised?
Don't forget.
Here you go.
Usually, I sell these
for thirty baht each,
but I'll give this to you for free.
For free?
Thirty baht?
Why did you rush over here?
Oh...
Here, ma'am.
I bought this for you.
I'm truly sorry.
Although this can't replace
your actual anniversary gift,
I still wanted to give it to you.
Actually, Soh bought it for me.
And it wasn't
an anniversary gift at all.
I'm sorry to you, too.
You look exhausted.
She's definitely
the most difficult boss to win.
Thank you, son.
I saw how much effort you put in.
Even if it really were
my wedding anniversary gift,
I wouldn't have minded.
Things can be lost,
but this precious son of mine...
can't be.
Don't you worry, Mom.
While regular jobs might have days off,
taking care of Soh is a job
I'll never take a break from
because I'm doing it from the heart.
Don't expect
any overtime pay from me, though.
Thank you so much, son.
No problem.
This sucks.
Hey, Ten.
Sorry, man.
All seats are taken.
Why don't you head back
with your old friends?
Oh, I forgot.
He doesn't have any friends.
A guy with no friends, huh?
Hey, we're just kidding.
I've got a spare seat for you.
Want to ride in our truck?
There's still some room for you.
If you want to come, you can.
You don't need to
swing back for me anymore.
I'm done heading
in the same direction as you guys.
What exactly do you mean by that?
You know exactly what I mean.
Dammit!
I'm not going to thank you for the ride.
Let's just call it even
since I helped you out, too.
Yeah.
See you in the next match, then.
If you're still with Blue Viper,
that is.
If I'm still with Blue Viper,
you won't stand a chance.
Ten...
Wait.
Aren't you heading back
with B.S. Brothers?
I don't feel very comfortable
sleeping at Soh's mom's place.
So what?
Want to stay the night with me?
Can't I just piggyback off you
and stay at a luxury hotel for once?
Just tell me what's really on your mind.
Well, the tournament is over now.
I'm just here to keep my promise.
So, what are you going to do next?
Are you going back to Blue Viper?
Probably not.
I want to take a break for a bit,
and then I'll find a place
where I actually belong.
Then just stay right here with me.
Don't you remember...
that a Jack card always belongs
right next to a Ten?
That's so cringe.
Come on.
I'm glad you and Three
are actually talking again
even if it's not on the best of terms.
But honestly,
back when we were all still friends,
we weren't exactly nice
to each other, either.
True.
But come to think of it,
you're kind of like a boxing referee.
Whenever Three and I got into it,
you always stayed neutral,
never taking sides.
I guess I was just being selfish,
wanting you to be on my side,
even when I was clearly
the one in the wrong.
I really hated it, man,
whenever you chose Three over me.
I want you to know...
that I never stopped choosing you.
When I started
distancing myself from you,
it wasn't because
I chose to be on his side.
I was going through some personal sh*t,
and I knew that if you found out,
you'd dive right in to help me
with everything you had.
I just didn't want
to feel pathetic, man,
having to let you fix my problems
over and over again.
And you know what?
I f*cking hated it...
when I was left all alone.
- We did it!
- Number one!
(I'm super excited right now,)
(and I'm really, really happy)
(that everyone voted for us
to be the MVPs.)
(Alright, thank you to all the fans)
(who voted for us...)
(Because I don't want to play
with you guys anymore!)
(Goddammit!)
I just felt like you and Three
were slowly drifting away from me.
Further and further away...
until the distance between us
grew huge.
So huge that sometimes
I felt like I was all alone.
I screwed everyone over.
I did you dirty.
I did Three dirty.
I just felt so much pain
because I thought my wounds
were the deepest in the world...
to the point where I started thinking
that maybe it was okay...
to hurt others just to protect myself.
That's why I chose
to betray you and everyone.
I'm sorry...
if I ever made you feel that way.
I should apologize to everyone.
And you...
Can I come back to you now?
I told you I'd be by your side,
and I will stay...
even on the days
when you're not on your own side.
Remember that.
We should bring
P'Toobtub and P'Jane next time.
Exactly. If P'Toobtub were here,
we wouldn't have to pay for the booze.
And he could've helped
carry these suitcases, too.
- So heavy. No idea what's in here.
- Yeah.
Wait, where's Jack?
I haven't seen him since last night.
P'Jack?
I called him last night.
He said he'd catch up with us.
I've got his suitcase right here.
It's heavy as f*ck.
I know.
What the hell did he pack?
Speak of the devil. There he is.
Hey!
- Whoa!
- Hey, hi!
Alright, okay.
- Goodbye. Thank you for having us.
- Goodbye.
- We're heading off now. Goodbye.
- Goodbye!
Let's go, Soh.
P'Three...
Let's stay in Chiang Mai a bit longer.
Just the two of us.
I've already rescheduled our flights.
Wow, someone's going to have a blast.
Have a great trip, you two,
now that you won't have
any third wheels like us.
Oh, wait! We haven't even
been to Tha Phae yet.
- I've got an idea.
- Whoa, wait! No.
- Just go home.
- Guess I'll just head back, then.
Yeah.
- You want to get rid of me that badly?
- No, I love being with you.
- Go. Just get out of here.
- Alright. We're off. See ya!
See ya.
Goodbye!
I seriously can't believe him.
Well, enjoy your trip.
Thanks, Mom.
Goodbye.
Come here, give me a hug.
- We're off. Goodbye and thank you.
- Bye-bye.
So, what should we do now?
Wanna go to the zoo?
How about coming to see
a capybara in my room?
♪Love isn't a game we play,♪
♪You can't just start again another day♪
Where are you taking me today, Derya?
Anywhere is fine
as long as I'm with you.
You're so sweet.
Give me a kiss. Come on.
Hurry up.
♪You're the only one in my heart♪
- Kiss...
- Give me a kiss.
Soh, I think something's wrong
with the sticky rice.
It sticks to everything.
Just like how I'm stuck on you.
It's not sticking to my hands at all.
Oops, it's sticking to your lips, too.
♪By doing this every single day♪
♪Even if you never look my way♪
♪(You never look my way)♪
This is what a romantic trip
should be like.
We haven't finished
the full experience yet, though.
Look at these fangs...
Fang-tas-tic...
- Do I look fang-tas-tic?
- Absolutely.
- Do I really look fang-tas-tic?
- Yes, really.
Thank you for not giving up, P'Three.
As long as I have you by my side,
I'll never give up on anything.
I'll always be here to support you.
I won't let your HP drop.
You're being cute again.
♪I'll find my way
into your heart one day,♪
♪Getting a little closer every day,♪
♪Before you even look my way,♪
♪Before you realize I'm here to stay♪
♪For now,
I'll just keep things brotherly♪
♪While caring for you secretly♪
♪I'll leave no signs for you to see♪
♪Until your heart makes room for me♪
♪The answer is you whenever I ask my heart,♪
♪Can't get over you though I try so hard♪
♪I'm afraid that love could pull us apart♪
♪If I'm the only one who's loving with all my heart♪
♪So many times I've rehearsed the line♪
♪To tell you that I wish you were mine,♪
♪But I turn into a coward every time
you look in my eyes♪
♪Maybe the risk is too high to take,♪
♪Just being near you is enough for my sake,♪
♪But my heart beats so fast that I can't fake♪
♪I'll find my way into your heart one day,♪
♪Getting a little closer every day,♪
♪Before you even look my way,♪
♪Before you realize I'm here to stay♪
♪For now, I'll just keep things brotherly♪
♪While caring for you secretly♪
♪I'll leave no signs for you to see♪
♪Until your heart makes room for me♪
MkvDrama.net